estudents.com 2003-12-05

# terms_policies

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operations of Estudents.com, we gather certain types of information about Estudents.com users. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how you may correct or change information that Estudents.com may collect. 

**Information Collected by Estudents.com**  
Estudents.com collects two types of information about users: personal information (such as name, e-mail address and demographic information) and aggregate information (such as information about how many users log on to our sites on a daily basis). 

**Personal Information**  
Personal information is collected when users voluntarily register for membership services. These services include certain site features, receiving electronic newsletters, receiving electronic promotions or advertisements, using community and communication services, answering surveys, purchasing items, and entering contests and other promotional opportunities provided on our sites. We may collect personal information from you in other areas of our sites, but we will provide on-screen notification that we are doing so. We may receive personal usage and demographic information from our third-party partners, and we also collect e-mail addresses from users who send us support mail or request technical or other help. This information enables Estudents.com to improve our sites to make your online visits more productive and enjoyable. 

**Aggregate Information**  
One method of collecting aggregate information about your activities online (such as the pages you access most frequently or the search terms you enter), and information volunteered by you (such as survey or registration information), is by tracking Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. The computers that deliver the Web pages to you automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address. Our sites record IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on our sites. We also create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows these parties to advertise more effectively, and allows you to receive advertisements that are most relevant to your personal interests. An advertiser will not know that you clicked its advertisement unless you voluntarily and explicitly permit us to provide such information. 

**Use of Information Collected by Estudents.com**  
Estudents.com uses the personal information we collect to improve the content of our sites; to customize the content and/or layout of our sites for each individual user; to notify users about updates to our sites or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to users; and to investigate violations of our terms and conditions of use. 

**Sharing Data with Third Parties** **  
**Estudents.com shares aggregate information with third parties for advertising, promotional, and site usage purposes. With user permission, Estudents.com accesses personal information on behalf of pre-screened third parties for marketing or promotional purposes. We will always request permission to share such information on our sites. You may elect not to participate by clicking the appropriate on-screen button. Estudents.com may also share personal information with consultants and affiliates for internal business purposes and may divulge personal information if such information is subpoenaed, or if Estudents.com believes that membership has been used to commit unlawful acts, or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another user or of the general public. In some situations, we will share your personal information, on a confidential basis, with third parties who perform a particular service on our behalf, such as sending e-mails. These parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the limited purpose of providing the particular service on our behalf. In addition, Estudents.com may receive personal usage and demographic information from third parties and uses this information to improve our products and services.

Occasionally, we may post the name of a user (for example, a contest winner) on one of our sites. Estudents.com will notify you of this possibility when you provide your information or, if possible, will notify you when the information is posted. 

Estudents.com may use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share web site usage information about visitors to our sites with such company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites. For this purpose, we and any third-party advertising company we may use, may note some of the pages you visit on our sites through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). 

**Electronic Newsletters**  
Some of our sites offer free, electronic newsletters as a service to our users. You will only receive a newsletter if you agree to receive it during registration to one of the areas of our sites or directly from our newsletter sign-up form. We will not divulge your membership in a newsletter mailing list to any third parties, including advertisers or partners, if you request that we not do so when you register. 

If you have registered through our online registration system and have subscribed to one or more of Estudents.com e-mail newsletters but do not want to continue receiving such e-mail newsletter(s), please send an e-mail to Unsubscribe@Estudents.com

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**  
Postageshop encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. At various places on our sites, we ask whether users are under the age of 18 or 13. Estudents.com relies on our users to be truthful in responding to these questions. 

**Individuals Under 13**  
No information should be submitted to or posted on our sites by users under the age of 13. Individuals under the age of 13 are not allowed to become registered users of our sites. 

**Individuals 13 Through 17**  
Estudents.com requests that children under the age of 18 not submit or post information to our sites. If an individual between the ages of 13 and 17 does so, Estudents.com may collect information (including personally identifying information). This information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Estudents.com and may, with the user's permission, be shared with pre-screened third parties. If a user or his/her parent or guardian changes his/her mind with respect to such use, that user, parent or guardian may stop that use either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our sites contain links to sites other than our own. Those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Estudents.com. Such links may be to advertisers, content providers or partners who may use our logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect information and use it in a way inconsistent with  Estudents.com privacy policy. Estudents.com does not control the content that appears on these sites. Such sites may contain information that content providers independent of Estudents.com have created, maintained, published, posted or otherwise made available. The use of any information or materials that you may access at these external sites is purely voluntary. You should not rely on their contents without independent and thorough review of the accuracy, completeness, effectiveness, timeliness and correct sequencing. These external sites may also refer to specific commercial products, processes, or services by trade name, trademark, service mark, manufacturer or otherwise. Unless Estudents.com has provided explicit authority, such references in no way indicate our endorsement, recommendation or preference. 

**Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Estudents.com, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

**Additional Information**  
No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Estudents.com to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, Estudents.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. 

Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall Estudents.com be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages that result from the use of the information or materials on our sites, even if Estudents.com or an authorized representative of Estudents.com, has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

Estudents.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted online. Questions should be directed to Info@Estudents.com
